sombra online
ah you'd make a good barista bastion
you know i've seen reinhardt's overwatch
file
what are you getting at i wonder if he's
really told you the truth about his
retirement
isn't it a little embarrassing to get
beaten up by a monkey
have you ever been hit by a giant
genetically engineered gorilla
i could arrange it for you
ooh i can't stand you hackers you give
those of us with skill a bad name
you know that isn't the kind of hacking
i do right
hey sombra i hear you're a master of
unlocking
what are you talking about
you wouldn't believe what i learned
about you sparrow
i am at peace with who i was your threat
does not concern me
now i've seen it all i'm supposed to
work with a giant rat
they don't pay me enough for this you
remind me of my stuffed bear arturito
i like him better
pleasure working with you mccree if that
is your real name
don't know what you heard but my name's
not joel
best remember that
started any wars lately i'd have to
check my schedule
i wonder what's locked up in that brain
of yours
my systems are protected by state of the
art
[Music]
farah ever wonder why you were never
accepted into overwatch
almost like someone didn't want you to
join have you ever considered getting a
new hobby
what's the plan today gabe you don't
mind if i call you gabe do you
stick to the mission
[Music]
try to stick to the plan sombra
look someone has to be ready when all
your careful planning doesn't pan out
so what are we doing here boss i need to
pay a visit to a friend
i saw you at calaveras they let you in
there
well i guess no one was going to stop
you
what interesting things i've learned
about your employers
miss faswani what have you heard
ah my favorite spider i
wonder what sort of web you're spinning
now it'd be a shame if something
happened to you on our next mission
a real pity
don't think i don't recognize that
device of yours i know you stole it what
can i say
a girl just has to have the latest tech
sometimes i feel a little sick after
using my translocator
i'm sure you know what i mean tracer
won't be a problem if you just disappear
forever
your friend katya volskaya what will you
say when you learn the truth
she's a hero to all russians i do not
care what you have to say
katya volskaya and alexandra sarianova
traitors to your own country you deserve
each other
i do what i must for my people
a